http://www.antique-silver.com/privacy-policy

We use cookies to make your experience better.
To comply with the new e-Privacy directive, we need to ask for your consent to set the cookies.
Learn more
Allow Cookies
The wishlist name can't be left blank
COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACYThis site is owned and operated by Sanda Lipton Antique Silver . Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Sanda Lipton Antique Silver we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. Definition of the Information Sanda Lipton Antique Silver gathers and keeps track of. Sanda Lipton Antique Silver gathers two types of information about users: · Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys:· Information that Sanda Lipton Antique Silver gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our site. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does Sanda Lipton Antique Silver divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.Sanda Lipton Antique Silver Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:Optional Voluntary InformationWe offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:1.  Electronic Newsletters/Mailshots (Dispatches). We will offer a free electronic newsletter/mailshot to users. Sanda Lipton Antique Silver gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter/mailshot that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.2.  "Email this to a friend" Service. Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "email this to a friend". The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.CHILDRENConsistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.COOKIESWe may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Sanda Lipton Antique Silver uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys.USE OF INFORMATIONSanda Lipton Antique Silver uses any information voluntarily given by our users to use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters/mailshot.We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter/mailshot), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing.  Sanda Lipton Antique Silver never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our site users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. SHARING OF THE INFORMATIONWe will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.OPT-OUT POLICYWe give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include: ·  Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters/mailshots. ·  Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our usersYOUR CONSENTBy using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Sanda Lipton Antique Silver . If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
